<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Danny Ayers' Blog</title>
    
    <link href="https://danny.ayers.name"/>
    <updated>2024-12-28T16:31:40.251Z</updated>
    <id>https://danny.ayers.name</id>
    <author>
        <name>Danny Ayers</name>
        <email>danny.ayers@gmail.com</email>
    </author>

    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-28_db</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-28_db.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-28_db.html</id>
        <updated>2024-12-28T16:31:40.251Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;DB&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I&amp;#39;ve got drum &amp;amp; bass playing&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brain slow today because I had a very late night. But I&amp;#39;m quite happy with that, because I actually made it into the music room for a couple of hours. I&amp;#39;m working on a suite of tracks that will share some common elements. What was the word for those 70s prog rock...gottit, I want to make a &lt;strong&gt;concept album&lt;/strong&gt;. Unlike virtually all the prog rocks, I want this thing to be interesting.
Anyway, there was a specific idea I wanted to try. The music room has often been painful recently, random bits of gear failing. So I was expecting to waste loads of time being the engineer. Except - everything worked a treat. I got a good first draft of the idea down. In the early hours, this particular part is at 160 bpm. After a couple of hours of that my body had gone a bit hyper. So I ended up taking Claudio for a walk at 5 am. Was enjoyable in a Blair Witch Project way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;tbox&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been doing a bit more on this. I need some advice on DNS handling, but to get that out of Claude I need to let him known what I&amp;#39;m trying to do with #:tbox.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I need your advice on DNS handling. Please consider the following description and tell me your recommendations. The goal of the tbox project is to create an intelligent agent ecosystem, including a knowledgebase, in a Docker container. It will interact with the outside world primarily through HTTP (using custom node services) and the XMPP protocol. It is intended to be used in two ways : as a development environment on a desktop computer or as an online service. Online, I plan to use a domain I control, &lt;code&gt;strandz.it&lt;/code&gt;, possibly with services on subdomains eg. &lt;code&gt;xmpp.strandz.it&lt;/code&gt;. I already have nginx set up on the server for routing with https support, so it&amp;#39;s fine for the Docker container to expose regular http &amp;amp; xmpp ports without encryption. Locally, a priority is to be able to do selective hot code updates while leaving other services on the container, eg. fuseki and prosody live.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok, after a few cycles Claude gave me some material that looks good, I&amp;#39;ve saved as-is under:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-sh&quot;&gt;/home/danny/github-danny/hyperdata/packages/tbox/docs/artifacts_2024-12-28
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-27_projects</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-27_projects.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-27_projects.html</id>
        <updated>2024-12-28T16:31:40.251Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Projects&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Project docs are a priority for me right now. But interdependencies are crazy-convoluted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First problem is identifying the projects...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of the things I&amp;#39;ve been most active with recently are still early-stage as Claude projects and/or on notes I&amp;#39;ve got scattered around, or in repos which appear two dirs on my office machine. I&amp;#39;ll get back to that later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First I need to remind myself where I was up to with :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:tbox - a Docker container for &lt;em&gt;stuff&lt;/em&gt;, most relevant right know, &lt;strong&gt;knowledgebases&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:semem - a &lt;strong&gt;knowledgebase interface&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;tbox&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hah! I&amp;#39;d got further than I remembered. The Job One &lt;a href=&quot;https://jena.apache.org/documentation/fuseki2/&quot;&gt;Fuseki SPARQL Server&lt;/a&gt; is already in place. Exposed at &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4030&quot;&gt;http://localhost:4030&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looks like I got &lt;a href=&quot;https://prosody.im/&quot;&gt;Prosody IM Server&lt;/a&gt; in there too, but I&amp;#39;m pretty sure I haven&amp;#39;t tested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I need to get #:transmissions and other core #:hyperdata projects in here too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because I need #:semem to organise my existing docs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I saved a link about setting up Docker as a dev container, best read that first.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;semem&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dog walk now, coffee with Mari &amp;amp; plumbing supplies run soon. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-sh&quot;&gt;github-danny$ ls
backup.sh         dogbot        elfquake.org           getting-things-diced-on-paper  hyperdata-static   ls.txt       postcraft                server_      strandz     transmissions
claude-sync       elfquake      foaf-retro             hyperdata                      hyperdata-support  markor-docs  postcraft-raw-hyperdata  sparqlpress  temp
danny.ayers.name  elfquake-old  foaf-retro-non-github  hyperdata-desktop_ex-packages  jsbrains           mcp-o        postcraft-support        StoneRDF     trans-apps

~/github-danny/hyperdata/packages$ ls
auth-test  common   dogbot  graph-editor       kia            ns                    progressive-scraper  server       sparql-store-lite  strandz  trans-dev  utils
chauvin    danping  farelo  hyperdata-android  ldap-auth-app  open-world-interface  semem                sheltopusik  store-wrapper      tbox     trellis
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-26_indigestion</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-26_indigestion.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-26_indigestion.html</id>
        <updated>2024-12-28T16:31:40.251Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Indigestion&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Despite in being traditional to overeat at this time of year, it&amp;#39;s not me but my code that&amp;#39;s got tummy ache.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog now has an &lt;a href=&quot;https://danny.ayers.name/atom.xml&quot;&gt;Atom Feed&lt;/a&gt;. I&amp;#39;ve only done an eyeball check, but it looks ok.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other night I had a quick stab at adding this. Claude gave me some convincing-looking code, which didn&amp;#39;t work. I only had a quick look then, it looked like it might take a while to fix. It turned out to be easy, but only once I&amp;#39;d figured out what my #:postcraft code (from months ago) was doing, which took ages. My bad, I&amp;#39;m not surprised Claude got things wrong, my stuff was well obfuscated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The immediate issue was in the handling of &lt;code&gt;manifest.ttl&lt;/code&gt;, the purpose of which in this case was to provide &lt;code&gt;danny.ayers.name&lt;/code&gt; site-specific information to the &lt;code&gt;postcraft&lt;/code&gt; #:transmissions application. I was already well aware that a bunch of &lt;strong&gt;refactoring&lt;/strong&gt; was needed around the &lt;code&gt;transmissions.ttl&lt;/code&gt;/&lt;code&gt;config.ttl&lt;/code&gt;/&lt;code&gt;manifest.ttl&lt;/code&gt; &lt;strong&gt;separation of concerns&lt;/strong&gt;. It turned out to be worse than I thought : the handling of &lt;code&gt;manifest.ttl&lt;/code&gt; was pretty much &lt;strong&gt;hardcoded&lt;/strong&gt; in &lt;code&gt;src/processors/rdf/ConfigMap.js&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Ops!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get a feed rendering, as a quick workaround I copy &amp;amp; pasted the method that handled the &lt;strong&gt;RDF resource&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;code&gt;t:IndexPage&lt;/code&gt; and tweaked for &lt;code&gt;t:AtomFeed&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not pretty, but it&amp;#39;ll do for now. That was a useful exercise, it added another flag to a specific group of #:todos, pushing up their priority in my head. What it &lt;strong&gt;should&lt;/strong&gt; have done is push up the priorities declared in the project description, managed by #:farelo. Which pushes the in-progress #:farelo up priorities (in my head).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Associated with that is &lt;strong&gt;all project docs&lt;/strong&gt;, already high on my priorities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not in the mood for being systematic today, but today that&amp;#39;s fine. To get the docs together I need to poke around with all the subprojects, remind myself where I&amp;#39;m at, write down their descriptions, current status &amp;amp; todos (which will ultimately be fed into #:farelo).
I can pick any part I fancy to play around with and in doing so I&amp;#39;m doing something that will be close to critical paths.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But right now, #:dogwalk #2 before it gets dark.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-23_sites</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-23_sites.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-23_sites.html</id>
        <updated>2024-12-28T16:31:40.251Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Sites&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t want to break any URLs on my sites as they stand, but I&amp;#39;ve got loads of (currently badly organised) material to add, mostly project docs which will be rendered through #:postcraft. Everything is going on the same Ubuntu server. Right now the material is mostly split per-project in repos on GitHub. I reckon the raw material (mostly markdown) is best left where it is, but the rendered versions can all go all go together. Pretty all the new stuff should go under the umbrella (and domain name) of &lt;a href=&quot;https://hyperdata.it&quot;&gt;hyperdata.it&lt;/a&gt;. The older material I have that&amp;#39;s actually live now is in the repo &lt;code&gt;hyperdata-static&lt;/code&gt;, I&amp;#39;ll leave that alone. But I do have a more recent repo &lt;code&gt;hyperdata&lt;/code&gt;, with a lot of the current (sub-)projects as git submodules. So to keep things simple, for now I&amp;#39;ll have #:postcraft render the corresponding docs under the local dir :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-sh&quot;&gt;~/github-danny/hyperdata/site
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hmm. A slight complication is that I&amp;#39;ve also got non-postcraft docs, &lt;code&gt;jsdoc&lt;/code&gt; etc. Postcraft will be providing the index page etc, so I guess the easiest is to go for eg. :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-sh&quot;&gt;# postcraft
~/github-danny/hyperdata/site/transmissions/index.html
~/github-danny/hyperdata/site/transmissions/entries/2024-12-23_today.html`
...

# non-postcraft
~/github-danny/hyperdata/site/transmissions/jsdoc
~/github-danny/hyperdata/site/transmissions/jsdoc/index.html
...
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of the new material will want the same kind of layout/styling, so I&amp;#39;d better also have a :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-sh&quot;&gt;~/github-danny/hyperdata/site/common
~/github-danny/hyperdata/site/common/css
...
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can do the routing via symlinks on the server and/or nginx routing. There might be some existing potential conflicts, eg. there could well be a &lt;code&gt;https://hyperdata.it/transmissions&lt;/code&gt; already. But I don&amp;#39;t need to worry about that right away. First get the stuff rendering in an organised fashion, figure out the plumbing later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of plumbing, I&amp;#39;ve a toilet cistern over at No.7 to fix today if I can (might need new parts). The power&amp;#39;s off over there at the moment so I should take advantage of the daylight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#:todo check ufw status on server&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#:breakpoint&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-23_eat-me</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-23_eat-me.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-23_eat-me.html</id>
        <updated>2024-12-28T16:31:40.251Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Eat Me&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m sorting out docs, one thing I remembered I don&amp;#39;t have in place yet is a syndication feed for these things. An absolute &lt;strong&gt;didn&amp;#39;t I do that aready?&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like, &lt;strong&gt;I have history&lt;/strong&gt; in this space. I caught the tail end of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/History_of_web_syndication_technology&quot;&gt;RSS wars&lt;/a&gt;. Such a daft (multi-fronted) war. Initially I was religiously RSS 1.0, the RDF. But despite my dogmatism, I was already aware at the time how awful RDF/XML was as a format in practice. It was an easy one to get sucked into, I was enchanted by the RDF model (still am, a sweetspot IMO, but it did need Turtle syntax and named graphs to properly make it viable for a regular dev). Good folks I knew were on &lt;strong&gt;that side&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dave_Winer&quot;&gt;Dave Winer&lt;/a&gt; could be such a massively annoying arse. Really really massively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In retrospect, respect where it&amp;#39;s due, Winer did push things forward. Ok, a lot of that was in folks thinking about how to do this thing right, to counter his approach, which had an overabundance of ego at it&amp;#39;s heart. That was a bit annoying itself, an intelligent, creative guy, you know I could begrudgingly call him  &lt;strong&gt;visionary&lt;/strong&gt;. Except it was overshadowed by narcissism and belligerence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heh, I nearly put &amp;quot;IMHO&amp;quot; there. But that reminds me of an interchange I had with him where he was incredibly dismissive of my points, passive-aggressively using Valley acronyms. I responded with &amp;quot;UYB&amp;quot;. I had made it up on the spur. But apparently it had made it into the urban dics, I lost the high ground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But with the naming of &lt;strong&gt;RSS 2.0&lt;/strong&gt; he showed some serious genious. Marketing-wise, awesome.     &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, back to &lt;strong&gt;my&lt;/strong&gt; ego. I&amp;#39;ve contributed content to 10 printed books. The only one I was the lead author on was &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Beginning-Atom-Programming-Danny-Ayers/dp/0764579169&quot;&gt;Beginning RSS and Atom Programming&lt;/a&gt;. Heh, combined rating of 1.6 on reviews there.
It was probably pretty good. Not through my efforts directly, but Wrox Press at the time had a legion of expert/expert-ish reviewers that forced you to revise, think, revise. Also Andrew was very good at his stuff. I can&amp;#39;t check, I gave all the copies I had away... oh wait, I might have the Turkish translation...(&lt;em&gt;mouldy shelves...&lt;/em&gt;)
Nope. That is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Web-2-0-Teknolojileri-Eric-Vlist/dp/975297855X/&quot;&gt;Web 2.0 Teknolojileri&lt;/a&gt;. Wtf did I do for that? Was the same period as the RSS. Probably something with that, shoehorning in RDF somehow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh yeah. Gorblimey, quite a lot of this looks like my stuff. &lt;strong&gt;FOAF!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the decade or so I was doing the freelance writing stuff, I did learn how to play the publishers somewhat. &lt;strong&gt;Engage the reviewer, not the reader&lt;/strong&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Code examples in Python ffs. So I must have learnt a little bit of it at some point before forgetting it again. Also XSLT involved (on RDF/XML, eek!). But XSLT was a good language, despite the horror syntax. &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jeni_Tennison&quot;&gt;Jeni Tennison&lt;/a&gt; frequently sent me dizzy with the elegance she pulled out of the hat.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is surprising what still lives. I recently rediscovered this &lt;a href=&quot;https://hyperdata.it/xmlns/pets/&quot;&gt;Pet Profiles&lt;/a&gt; thing I did in, er...2004. Most of the associated code around there is now totally broken. But &lt;a href=&quot;https://hyperdata.it/xmlns/pets/2004-04-24/sambuca-css.xml&quot;&gt;Sambuca&amp;#39;s Profile&lt;/a&gt;, using CSS on RDF/XML, sweet. Has exactly the same little layout probs I didn&amp;#39;t get around to fixing 20 years ago.   &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;I&amp;#39;ve not quite finished with my ego&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So in this fog of RSS war, some righteous folks came up with a cunning plan: &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Atom_(web_standard)&quot;&gt;Atom&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I get an ack on &lt;a href=&quot;https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc4287&quot;&gt;RFC4287&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OK, ego spent.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was all-in with Atom Format, but kind-of backstepped out of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc5023&quot;&gt;Protocol, RFC5023&lt;/a&gt;. I&amp;#39;d love to say it was because I saw the redundancy of that on top of &lt;strong&gt;Fielding-compliant REST&lt;/strong&gt;, but really it was because the other folks were shitloads better at protocols, I was out of my depth, had nothing to offer. &lt;em&gt;In retrospect&lt;/em&gt;, good move. Now I see the redundancy. And the Web stage has shifted to make absolutely awful practices that have issues dating back to &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SOAP&quot;&gt;SOAP&lt;/a&gt;. I&amp;#39;m sure, hope and pray (in an atheistic manner)  &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tim_Berners-Lee&quot;&gt;timbl&lt;/a&gt; has many years left on this mortal coil, because he has a hella lotta grave-spinning backed up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, in retrospect, Atom was the right idea. The folks around microformats, (hat tip &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tantek_%C3%87elik&quot;&gt;Tantek&lt;/a&gt;) had a valid point that HTML could easily carry the same information just as easily, no need for a different content format. But pragmatically, one sliver of a little toenail towards the Winer, it does now make sense to use a different format. I can still get on a high horse about content negotiation being there if you want it, &lt;strong&gt;so merrr!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#:todo check media types/extensions known by nginx&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, however long ago I got to desk this session, I had feed on mind. This is a nice little exercise. With my current workflow &amp;amp; tooling, &lt;strong&gt;how long will it take me to add a feed&lt;/strong&gt; to this site?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On my own I would guess maybe 2 very stumbly hours. I have to remember how to use the templater I&amp;#39;ve got here, I&amp;#39;ve not looked at for a few months (&lt;a href=&quot;https://mozilla.github.io/nunjucks/&quot;&gt;nunjucks&lt;/a&gt; - it looked best at the time) and also some of my own code from a day ago... (#:adhd is a thing).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I don&amp;#39;t want to waste my own scant cognitive resources on something like this. Claude understands my setup, I made it so for his kind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#:timestamp 23:58&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(I will need a pee, cigarette and another mug of beer first, dear Countdown Clock)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
</feed>