<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Danny Ayers' Blog</title>
    
    <link href="https://danny.ayers.name"/>
    <updated>2025-01-02T12:19:48.493Z</updated>
    <id>https://danny.ayers.name</id>
    <author>
        <name>Danny Ayers</name>
        <email>danny.ayers@gmail.com</email>
    </author>

    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2025-01-02_fix-deploy</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2025-01-02_fix-deploy.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2025-01-02_fix-deploy.html</id>
        <updated>2025-01-02T12:19:48.493Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Semem Fix &amp;amp; Deploy&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made a todo list here yesterday without any explanation. Didn&amp;#39;t publish. Invisible todo list is absolutely not what I want on my blog front page! My top priority this week is doc organisation, so I&amp;#39;ll let myself off this time. I&amp;#39;ve changed the date on the file, this is it I&amp;#39;ll now fill it out...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A little job for this morning is a little explore of &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/danja/semem&quot;&gt;Semem&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It appears to (mostly) work, here&amp;#39;s the &lt;a href=&quot;https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2025-01-01_semem-run.html&quot;&gt;console log of a run&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, &lt;strong&gt;what is it doing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What I want right now, as a bit of scaffolding for what I want to explore, is a nodejs version of &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/caspianmoon/memoripy&quot;&gt;memoripy&lt;/a&gt; that uses a (remote) SPARQL store as (part of) its knowledgebase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I only tried running it after many hours implementing it in a Claude project. Then had a couple of hours manually tweaking to get it to (mostly) run. It&amp;#39;s definitely interacting with Ollama for embeddings &amp;amp; chat, a SPARQL endpoint for persistence. I don&amp;#39;t see the extracted concepts in the SPARQL store.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last night I had a short session with Claude, aiming to document what we had so far. I&amp;#39;ve put the artifacts over here : &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/danja/semem/tree/main/docs/description_2025-01-01.md&quot;&gt;https://github.com/danja/semem/tree/main/docs/description_2025-01-01.md&lt;/a&gt; It sounds marvellous, but how much is true?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Banebane&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had a chat with ClaudioB yesterday morning, pointed him to my notes so far on #:semem. He asked me if I had a &lt;strong&gt;live instance&lt;/strong&gt; he could play with. A very good question! Not for the first time I&amp;#39;ll quote -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Connolly&amp;#39;s Bane&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;quot;The bane of my existence is doing things that I know the
computer could do for me&amp;quot;&lt;/strong&gt;
&#92;– Dan Connolly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Which reminded me I&amp;#39;ve not been in touch with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ninebynine.org/&quot;&gt;Graham Klyne&lt;/a&gt; for many years. A blog post of his drew my attention to that quote. Good-o, he&amp;#39;s on Mastodon : &lt;a href=&quot;https://indieweb.social/@gklyne&quot;&gt;@gklyne@indieweb.social&lt;/a&gt;, I&amp;#39;ll ping him there.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ClaudioB&amp;#39;s question is the kind of message I want my #:hyperdata systems to be able to deal with automatically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s how this human agent is handling it :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[prompt]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is there a live instance of Semem?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[me]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;immediate response, &amp;quot;not yet&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;reformulate question in terms of concrete requirements
-&amp;gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(functioning, good-enough) Semem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;hosting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;deployment infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For 1 : all I really need to do right away is minor bugfixing and whatever&amp;#39;s needed to use existing online LLMs
For 2 : I&amp;#39;ve got a live Ubuntu server (which you are looking at now) and a domain name registered for a related plan, some nginx proxying already in place.&lt;br&gt;For 3 : I&amp;#39;ve got a Docker container in-progress for this stuff, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/danja/tbox&quot;&gt;tbox&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;meta-reasoning - evaluate this against existing dev paths, consider priorities, time needed etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On this point there&amp;#39;s a green flag to go ahead, it&amp;#39;s near-enough in line with what I was planning to do already, slight rearrangement of immediate priorities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I acted in several roles there. Humans are good at this. I want a community of independent autonomous intelligent agents (on #:kia).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ops. Azzurra just reminded me that I&amp;#39;ve an appointment with her up at the comune at 15:00. Now 13:12. Clever Azzurra has me sussed. I&amp;#39;d completely forgotten. But she&amp;#39;s given me just the right amount of time to pop this online, take Claudio out for a short walk, find some clean clothes &amp;amp; have a wash.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Soon...&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Somewhere around my vocabs I need terms for this particular kind of input. I may already have something like &lt;strong&gt;Feature Request&lt;/strong&gt; around the project management oriented bits, but it totally ties in with agent-oriented messaging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo fix #:semem failing on UPDATE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo tease next steps from &lt;code&gt;semem/docs/description_2024-12-30/&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I sorted out the UPDATE.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;#:todo deploy to #:tbox&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;#:todo #:spike for function/action calling a la ReAct&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;#:todo some FOAF&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Installed &amp;#39;Markdown Preview Mermaid Support&amp;#39; into VSCode&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;semem - query execution times, store metrics, total embeddings size&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;support Groq, Mistral, Claude, OpenAI&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;refactor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;comments&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;install the willison-mentioned UI tool - has useful bits for APIs?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ditto LibreChat&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LOGGER - see Perplexity&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2025-01-01_semem-run</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2025-01-01_semem-run.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2025-01-01_semem-run.html</id>
        <updated>2025-01-02T12:19:48.493Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;node src/SPARQLExample.js

[INFO] Initialized FAISS index with dimension 1536
[INFO] Loaded 1 short-term and 0 long-term memories from store http://localhost:4030/test/query graph &amp;lt;http://example.org/mcp/memory&amp;gt;
[INFO] Adding interaction: &amp;#39;What&amp;#39;s the current state of the Semantic Web?&amp;#39;
[INFO] Memory initialized with 1 short-term and 0 long-term memories
[INFO] Extracting concepts...
[INFO] Extracted concepts: [ &amp;#39;Semantic Web technologies&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;AI&amp;#39; ]
[INFO] Retrieving relevant interactions...
Response: Semantic Web technologies and Artificial Intelligence (AI) complement each other well, as they are both powerful tools for representing complex data in structured form, facilitating knowledge discovery and enhancing human-computer interaction. Here are some ways in which semantic Web technologies can be integrated with AI:

1. **Knowledge Extraction from Semantically-Structured Data**: Semantic Web technologies provide a standardized way of defining and storing the structured information necessary to build semantic web applications. The use of these tools allows for the extraction of knowledge about large amounts of data, making it easier for AI systems to process this information.

2. **Artificial Intelligence as a Knowledge Broker**: AI can be used to curate and organize vast amounts of data in semantic Web formats. This includes tasks such as categorizing documents, recognizing patterns and relationships within structured data sets, and integrating heterogeneous data sources into a single knowledge base.

3. **Interactive Experience Enhancement through AI-Driven Semantic Web Applications**: AI-driven applications can provide a more personalized user experience by using techniques like recommendation systems to suggest content based on the user&amp;#39;s interests or previous behavior. These systems also use semantic Web technologies to ensure that the information presented is accurate and relevant to the user, enhancing their overall satisfaction with the application.

4. **Machine Learning for Enhanced AI Capabilities**: AI can be trained with data from large volumes of structured web documents, which can then be used to improve AI models’ understanding of context, language, and relationships within web content. This integration allows machines to learn complex patterns in unstructured or semi-structured data, further enhancing their ability to perform tasks that require human-like reasoning.

5. **Integration with Natural Language Processing (NLP) Systems**: Semantic Web technologies can be used with AI NLP systems to extract meaning from unstructured text and improve the understanding of natural language queries by machines. This integration allows for a more effective interaction between humans and computers, as the data is presented in a format that is easier for AI systems to interpret.

6. **Knowledge Management for Autonomous Agents**: Semantic Web technologies can be utilized with artificial intelligence-driven agents to store large volumes of structured information. These agents are capable of processing complex queries, making decisions, and performing tasks based on this knowledge. By integrating semantic web technologies into AI systems, we can create more intelligent autonomous agents that are better equipped to handle complex scenarios.

These integration strategies illustrate how the capabilities of both Semantic Web technologies and Artificial Intelligence can be combined to enhance our ability to process large volumes of information and solve complex problems efficiently.
[INFO] Extracting concepts...
[INFO] Extracted concepts: [
  &amp;#39;Semantic Web technologies&amp;#39;,
  &amp;#39;Artificial Intelligence (AI)&amp;#39;,
  &amp;#39;Knowledge Extraction from Semantically-Structured Data&amp;#39;,
  &amp;#39;Artificial Intelligence as a Knowledge Broker&amp;#39;,
  &amp;#39;Interactive Experience Enhancement through AI-Driven Semantic Web Applications&amp;#39;,
  &amp;#39;Machine Learning for Enhanced AI Capabilities&amp;#39;,
  &amp;#39;Integration with Natural Language Processing (NLP) Systems&amp;#39;,
  &amp;#39;Knowledge Management for Autonomous Agents&amp;#39;
]
[INFO] Adding interaction: &amp;#39;How can Semantic Web technologies be used with AI?&amp;#39;
[INFO] Saved memory to SPARQL store http://localhost:4030/test/update graph &amp;lt;http://example.org/mcp/memory&amp;gt;. Stats: 2 short-term, 0 long-term memories
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This query gives one result, containing the prompt &amp;amp; response from the above :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-sparql&quot;&gt;PREFIX mcp: &amp;lt;http://purl.org/stuff/mcp/&amp;gt;
SELECT ?graph ?id ?prompt ?output ?timestamp
WHERE {
  GRAPH ?graph {
  ?s a mcp:Interaction ;
     mcp:id ?id ;
     mcp:prompt ?prompt ;
     mcp:output ?output ;
     mcp:timestamp ?timestamp .
    FILTER regex(str(?prompt), &amp;quot;Semantic&amp;quot;)
}
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This gives 2 results :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-sparql&quot;&gt;SELECT *
WHERE {
  GRAPH ?graph {
  ?s ?p ?o
    FILTER regex(str(?o), &amp;quot;Semantic&amp;quot;)
}
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One is the triple with the prompt, the other the triple with the LLM output.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2025-01-01_hny</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2025-01-01_hny.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2025-01-01_hny.html</id>
        <updated>2025-01-02T12:19:48.493Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Happy New Year!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Foggy brain yet again. Not for the first time on New Year&amp;#39;s Day, but irritatingly I wasn&amp;#39;t up all that late and didn&amp;#39;t drink to excess. I did have fun last night, my first attempt at livestreaming. Around 7pm I was feeling blocked at desk (my head, not the code) and an idea formed in my head. I&amp;#39;d been listening to Drum &amp;amp; Bass. Didn&amp;#39;t seem right, hmm, bagpipes? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GjdnGNfDyd4&quot;&gt;Big Bad Bollocks&lt;/a&gt;? Pogues? Hang on, is there any D&amp;amp;B in 3/4 or 6/8 time? I decided to make some. By midnight.    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Easiest camera to set up was my Android phone (after I spent half an hour sorting out a tripod). Perplexity suggested Facebook was the easiest platform, but neglected to tell me it has a very confusing UI with sod all settings accessible. Worst, whatever resolution/codec it uses, it&amp;#39;s a network glutton. I&amp;#39;m not sure how much actually got streamed, 50% of the times I checked it was waiting to connect.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-31_semem-poc</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-31_semem-poc.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-31_semem-poc.html</id>
        <updated>2025-01-02T12:19:48.493Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Semem POC&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;First-thing morning ramblings, deep sea trawling for actionables again&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have two upcoming deadlines I&amp;#39;ve set myself:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:PoggiPivot 2025-01-05 - get my #:hyperdata project docs sorted&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:ProofPivot 2025-01-14 - proofs of concept for projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both racing towards me. But that&amp;#39;s the whole idea, use the purely artificial urgency to motivate myself to &lt;strong&gt;focus&lt;/strong&gt;. Success at achieving the goals is secondary, reflected in the fact I haven&amp;#39;t actually written down those criteria yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, since setting these I&amp;#39;ve made a good start on them for &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/danja/semem&quot;&gt;Semem&lt;/a&gt; (Semantic Memory). Which has highlighted one particular flaw in my current processes, that &lt;strong&gt;proof of concept&lt;/strong&gt; isn&amp;#39;t actually the phrase I intended in the above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Somewhere&lt;/em&gt;, probably in a Claude project, hopefully condensed in a vocab, I have (work on) better terms. But I need to get my docs sorted...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The phrase is/should be closer to &lt;strong&gt;minimum viable product&lt;/strong&gt;. But I don&amp;#39;t like this phrase because &lt;strong&gt;product&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;in this context, in my mind&lt;/em&gt; suggests a marketable commodity. As a dyed in the wool Capitalism-sceptic, I have a knee-jerk reaction to this kind of thing. In society at large there is an overarching conflation between a thing&amp;#39;s value in a &amp;quot;noble&amp;quot; utilitarian sense and it&amp;#39;s bottom line &lt;strong&gt;$ value&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aside&lt;/strong&gt; : I have a vague memory of having the same kind of reaction while tech-reviewing some book material by &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shelley_Powers&quot;&gt;Shelley Powers&lt;/a&gt; a good few years ago. &lt;em&gt;(This may be a completely false memory, apologies to Shelley if that&amp;#39;s the case, but it is plausible and moreover nicely fits this narrative, &amp;quot;don&amp;#39;t let the truth get in way...&amp;quot; and all that).&lt;/em&gt;  Shelley is one of my heros of the Web-tech world, and a bloody good writer. But in this particular chapter she made repeated use of phrases like &amp;quot;business rules&amp;quot;. Which I repeatedly criticised. There is a legitimate definition of &amp;quot;business&amp;quot; in this context, to paraphrase &amp;quot;the important stuff&amp;quot;. But still in my mind the conflation with business in the common-English commercial activity sense made my hackles rise. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Btw, I am an experienced reviewer, and key to that role is drawing attention to text that &lt;em&gt;might not&lt;/em&gt; be quite right. It might well be fine. But I&amp;#39;d say the diligent reviewer should err a little on the side of caution, flag things where suspicions are raised. As an experienced writer, Shelley would know many of such flags were tentative, a legitimate response being to reject them after a cursory mental check - which she probably did in this instance, if it ever happened. For sure, iffy crit is a pain and any crit can be demoralising when you get a downpour (I&amp;#39;d be one of many reviewers doing this). But the patience of Job and thick skin are job requirements.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any road... I do hope I did get some clear and accurate terminology nailed down for POC/MVC. Neutral language in the sense of not carrying misleading baggage. What I&amp;#39;m after is more like &amp;quot;demonstration of utility&amp;quot;. &lt;strong&gt;Clunky, eh&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Semem Demonstration of Utility&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I delighted myself with the hubris I got into my working description of #:semem :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/danja/semem&quot;&gt;Semem&lt;/a&gt; is an LLM-compatible context-aware, open-ended graph knowledgebase system combining the advantages of vector embeddings and Linked Data technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But what am I aiming for by 2025-01-14? I actually have an immediate use case with low-end requirements :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A system I can point to my local FS containing scattered markdown notes etc etc so I can use the stuff efficiently.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I reckon a baseline #:Semem needs to :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;provide simple similarity search&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;cluster related topics at different scales&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;create quasi-formalised annotation (metadata)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;make a disorganised, heterogenous corpus addressable as a coherent entity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;exploit LLMs (and maybe trad reasoning) to facilitate new knowledge discovery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok, I have some actionables. Mari&amp;#39;s picking me up in 15 mins to go for a coffee and I&amp;#39;m not yet out of bed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-30_todos</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-30_todos.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-30_todos.html</id>
        <updated>2025-01-02T12:19:48.494Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Todos&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;No todos los trabajos&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oddments for &lt;strong&gt;soon&lt;/strong&gt; I might easily forget.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:foaf from wget &lt;a href=&quot;https://prod-dcd-datasets-cache-zipfiles.s3.eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/zp23s23xpb-1.zip&quot;&gt;https://prod-dcd-datasets-cache-zipfiles.s3.eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/zp23s23xpb-1.zip&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo check pivot terms - write for #:PoggiPivot &amp;amp; #:ProofPivot. Use &amp;#39;inflection point&amp;#39; in docs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo form-a-matic - make my index.rdf&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo #:squirt to #:tbox&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo #:semem to #:tbox&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo block diagrams - Claude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo pull descriptions from memoripy &amp;amp; trustgraph&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo GitHub ci/CD&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo docker dev env&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo #:postcraft CSS initial size&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo #:postcraft fix links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo #:postcraft figure out #:semtags flow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo #:transmissions generate type definitions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
</feed>