<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Danny Ayers' Blog</title>
    
    <link href="https://danny.ayers.name"/>
    <updated>2024-12-29T11:10:53.562Z</updated>
    <id>https://danny.ayers.name</id>
    <author>
        <name>Danny Ayers</name>
        <email>danny.ayers@gmail.com</email>
    </author>

    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-29_sunny-day</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-29_sunny-day.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-29_sunny-day.html</id>
        <updated>2024-12-29T11:10:53.562Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Sunny Day&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It&amp;#39;s a sunny Sunday day.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My must-dos for today are plumbing. Actual plumbing :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sealant on leaky pipe at No.7&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix the &lt;em&gt;second&lt;/em&gt; hole I hadn&amp;#39;t seen under the sink here at #:New place&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also really need to make a start on some tree removal while the weather&amp;#39;s dry. Stretching the notion of plumbing, first I need to sort out climbing gear, ropes, pulleys etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Financial plumbing, I need to sort a stack of papers, find the relevant forms I have somewhere, to sort out pension flow from Derbyshire County Council. I had a small (but very useful) monthly sum coming from there. Caroline worked at a DCC special needs place for a few years, I inherited her pension. It stalled a couple of months ago, I missed some kind of update step. I did do a little towards sorting it out, in the process discovered that I&amp;#39;m probably due some funds from the years I worked at High Peak College.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Software plumbing...things to join together. Separate posts here for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-29_pivots</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-29_pivots.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-29_pivots.html</id>
        <updated>2024-12-29T11:10:53.562Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Pivots&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thinking aloud to find the actionables&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two artificial deadlines I want to set myself. I&amp;#39;ve got some vocab in-progress for expressing these, the term being #:pivot. There are two dates coming soon for good markers :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Poggi Pivot : Mari&amp;#39;s birthday, 2024-01-05&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proof Pivot : my birthday, 2024-01-14&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first one, primary goal is getting &lt;strong&gt;some&lt;/strong&gt; docs online for &lt;strong&gt;all&lt;/strong&gt; my currently active projects. Skeleton summaries/placeholders at minimum, the #:what, a little #:how. But I really want to capture how they relate to each other, the #:why. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second one, primary goal is creating a proof-of-concept for each project. The minimum here again is little more than skeletal placeholders. But again, capture of the interrelations is the part I&amp;#39;m aiming for. Get the overall dependency graph formalised enough that it can be used in planning. It&amp;#39;s twisty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok, I&amp;#39;ve got actionables (not far off what I was doing already). For #:PoggiPivot, first step is to wire up all the #:postcraft spaces, make them live.
In quasi-parallel, towards #:ProofPivot, two must-haves : write down core project description for each, maybe in a proposal-like form; write down the #:poc requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This lot in itself is a major grind. But I need to remind myself where I&amp;#39;m up to with everything. Best way to do this and keep it interesting is to see what I have noted for next step #:todos, code up the next little step.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just did this with #:tbox. While going over it with Claude he gave me an architectural diagram (in Mermaid format) which I found really helpful. I&amp;#39;ve already got visualisations on the lists, but I reckon this is an aspect I should revisit very soon, to help with &lt;em&gt;everything else&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-28_db</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-28_db.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-28_db.html</id>
        <updated>2024-12-29T11:10:53.563Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;DB&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I&amp;#39;ve got drum &amp;amp; bass playing&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brain slow today because I had a very late night. But I&amp;#39;m quite happy with that, because I actually made it into the music room for a couple of hours. I&amp;#39;m working on a suite of tracks that will share some common elements. What was the word for those 70s prog rock...gottit, I want to make a &lt;strong&gt;concept album&lt;/strong&gt;. Unlike virtually all the prog rocks, I want this thing to be interesting.
Anyway, there was a specific idea I wanted to try. The music room has often been painful recently, random bits of gear failing. So I was expecting to waste loads of time being the engineer. Except - everything worked a treat. I got a good first draft of the idea down. In the early hours, this particular part is at 160 bpm. After a couple of hours of that my body had gone a bit hyper. So I ended up taking Claudio for a walk at 5 am. Was enjoyable in a Blair Witch Project way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;tbox&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been doing a bit more on this. I need some advice on DNS handling, but to get that out of Claude I need to let him known what I&amp;#39;m trying to do with #:tbox.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I need your advice on DNS handling. Please consider the following description and tell me your recommendations. The goal of the tbox project is to create an intelligent agent ecosystem, including a knowledgebase, in a Docker container. It will interact with the outside world primarily through HTTP (using custom node services) and the XMPP protocol. It is intended to be used in two ways : as a development environment on a desktop computer or as an online service. Online, I plan to use a domain I control, &lt;code&gt;strandz.it&lt;/code&gt;, possibly with services on subdomains eg. &lt;code&gt;xmpp.strandz.it&lt;/code&gt;. I already have nginx set up on the server for routing with https support, so it&amp;#39;s fine for the Docker container to expose regular http &amp;amp; xmpp ports without encryption. Locally, a priority is to be able to do selective hot code updates while leaving other services on the container, eg. fuseki and prosody live.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok, after a few cycles Claude gave me some material that looks good, I&amp;#39;ve saved as-is under:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-sh&quot;&gt;/home/danny/github-danny/hyperdata/packages/tbox/docs/artifacts_2024-12-28
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-27_projects</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-27_projects.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-27_projects.html</id>
        <updated>2024-12-29T11:10:53.564Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Projects&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Project docs are a priority for me right now. But interdependencies are crazy-convoluted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First problem is identifying the projects...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of the things I&amp;#39;ve been most active with recently are still early-stage as Claude projects and/or on notes I&amp;#39;ve got scattered around, or in repos which appear two dirs on my office machine. I&amp;#39;ll get back to that later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First I need to remind myself where I was up to with :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:tbox - a Docker container for &lt;em&gt;stuff&lt;/em&gt;, most relevant right know, &lt;strong&gt;knowledgebases&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:semem - a &lt;strong&gt;knowledgebase interface&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;tbox&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hah! I&amp;#39;d got further than I remembered. The Job One &lt;a href=&quot;https://jena.apache.org/documentation/fuseki2/&quot;&gt;Fuseki SPARQL Server&lt;/a&gt; is already in place. Exposed at &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4030&quot;&gt;http://localhost:4030&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looks like I got &lt;a href=&quot;https://prosody.im/&quot;&gt;Prosody IM Server&lt;/a&gt; in there too, but I&amp;#39;m pretty sure I haven&amp;#39;t tested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I need to get #:transmissions and other core #:hyperdata projects in here too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because I need #:semem to organise my existing docs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I saved a link about setting up Docker as a dev container, best read that first.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;semem&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dog walk now, coffee with Mari &amp;amp; plumbing supplies run soon. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-sh&quot;&gt;github-danny$ ls
backup.sh         dogbot        elfquake.org           getting-things-diced-on-paper  hyperdata-static   ls.txt       postcraft                server_      strandz     transmissions
claude-sync       elfquake      foaf-retro             hyperdata                      hyperdata-support  markor-docs  postcraft-raw-hyperdata  sparqlpress  temp
danny.ayers.name  elfquake-old  foaf-retro-non-github  hyperdata-desktop_ex-packages  jsbrains           mcp-o        postcraft-support        StoneRDF     trans-apps

~/github-danny/hyperdata/packages$ ls
auth-test  common   dogbot  graph-editor       kia            ns                    progressive-scraper  server       sparql-store-lite  strandz  trans-dev  utils
chauvin    danping  farelo  hyperdata-android  ldap-auth-app  open-world-interface  semem                sheltopusik  store-wrapper      tbox     trellis
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-26_indigestion</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-26_indigestion.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-26_indigestion.html</id>
        <updated>2024-12-29T11:10:53.564Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Indigestion&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Despite in being traditional to overeat at this time of year, it&amp;#39;s not me but my code that&amp;#39;s got tummy ache.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog now has an &lt;a href=&quot;https://danny.ayers.name/atom.xml&quot;&gt;Atom Feed&lt;/a&gt;. I&amp;#39;ve only done an eyeball check, but it looks ok.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other night I had a quick stab at adding this. Claude gave me some convincing-looking code, which didn&amp;#39;t work. I only had a quick look then, it looked like it might take a while to fix. It turned out to be easy, but only once I&amp;#39;d figured out what my #:postcraft code (from months ago) was doing, which took ages. My bad, I&amp;#39;m not surprised Claude got things wrong, my stuff was well obfuscated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The immediate issue was in the handling of &lt;code&gt;manifest.ttl&lt;/code&gt;, the purpose of which in this case was to provide &lt;code&gt;danny.ayers.name&lt;/code&gt; site-specific information to the &lt;code&gt;postcraft&lt;/code&gt; #:transmissions application. I was already well aware that a bunch of &lt;strong&gt;refactoring&lt;/strong&gt; was needed around the &lt;code&gt;transmissions.ttl&lt;/code&gt;/&lt;code&gt;config.ttl&lt;/code&gt;/&lt;code&gt;manifest.ttl&lt;/code&gt; &lt;strong&gt;separation of concerns&lt;/strong&gt;. It turned out to be worse than I thought : the handling of &lt;code&gt;manifest.ttl&lt;/code&gt; was pretty much &lt;strong&gt;hardcoded&lt;/strong&gt; in &lt;code&gt;src/processors/rdf/ConfigMap.js&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Ops!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get a feed rendering, as a quick workaround I copy &amp;amp; pasted the method that handled the &lt;strong&gt;RDF resource&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;code&gt;t:IndexPage&lt;/code&gt; and tweaked for &lt;code&gt;t:AtomFeed&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not pretty, but it&amp;#39;ll do for now. That was a useful exercise, it added another flag to a specific group of #:todos, pushing up their priority in my head. What it &lt;strong&gt;should&lt;/strong&gt; have done is push up the priorities declared in the project description, managed by #:farelo. Which pushes the in-progress #:farelo up priorities (in my head).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Associated with that is &lt;strong&gt;all project docs&lt;/strong&gt;, already high on my priorities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not in the mood for being systematic today, but today that&amp;#39;s fine. To get the docs together I need to poke around with all the subprojects, remind myself where I&amp;#39;m at, write down their descriptions, current status &amp;amp; todos (which will ultimately be fed into #:farelo).
I can pick any part I fancy to play around with and in doing so I&amp;#39;m doing something that will be close to critical paths.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But right now, #:dogwalk #2 before it gets dark.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
</feed>