<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Danny Ayers' Blog</title>
    
    <link href="https://danny.ayers.name"/>
    <updated>2024-12-31T10:52:28.626Z</updated>
    <id>https://danny.ayers.name</id>
    <author>
        <name>Danny Ayers</name>
        <email>danny.ayers@gmail.com</email>
    </author>

    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-31_semem-poc</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-31_semem-poc.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-31_semem-poc.html</id>
        <updated>2024-12-31T10:52:28.626Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Semem POC&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;First-thing morning ramblings, deep sea trawling for actionables again&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have two upcoming deadlines I&amp;#39;ve set myself:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:PoggiPivot 2025-01-05 - get my #:hyperdata project docs sorted&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:ProofPivot 2025-01-14 - proofs of concept for projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both racing towards me. But that&amp;#39;s the whole idea, use the purely artificial urgency to motivate myself to &lt;strong&gt;focus&lt;/strong&gt;. Success at achieving the goals is secondary, reflected in the fact I haven&amp;#39;t actually written down those criteria yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, since setting these I&amp;#39;ve made a good start on them for &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/danja/semem&quot;&gt;Semem&lt;/a&gt; (Semantic Memory). Which has highlighted one particular flaw in my current processes, that &lt;strong&gt;proof of concept&lt;/strong&gt; isn&amp;#39;t actually the phrase I intended in the above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Somewhere&lt;/em&gt;, probably in a Claude project, hopefully condensed in a vocab, I have (work on) better terms. But I need to get my docs sorted...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The phrase is/should be closer to &lt;strong&gt;minimum viable product&lt;/strong&gt;. But I don&amp;#39;t like this phrase because &lt;strong&gt;product&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;in this context, in my mind&lt;/em&gt; suggests a marketable commodity. As a dyed in the wool Capitalism-sceptic, I have a knee-jerk reaction to this kind of thing. In society at large there is an overarching conflation between a thing&amp;#39;s value in a &amp;quot;noble&amp;quot; utilitarian sense and it&amp;#39;s bottom line &lt;strong&gt;$ value&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aside&lt;/strong&gt; : I have a vague memory of having the same kind of reaction while tech-reviewing some book material by &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shelley_Powers&quot;&gt;Shelley Powers&lt;/a&gt; a good few years ago. &lt;em&gt;(This may be a completely false memory, apologies to Shelley if that&amp;#39;s the case, but it is plausible and moreover nicely fits this narrative, &amp;quot;don&amp;#39;t let the truth get in way...&amp;quot; and all that).&lt;/em&gt;  Shelley is one of my heros of the Web-tech world, and a bloody good writer. But in this particular chapter she made repeated use of phrases like &amp;quot;business rules&amp;quot;. Which I repeatedly criticised. There is a legitimate definition of &amp;quot;business&amp;quot; in this context, to paraphrase &amp;quot;the important stuff&amp;quot;. But still in my mind the conflation with business in the common-English commercial activity sense made my hackles rise. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Btw, I am an experienced reviewer, and key to that role is drawing attention to text that &lt;em&gt;might not&lt;/em&gt; be quite right. It might well be fine. But I&amp;#39;d say the diligent reviewer should err a little on the side of caution, flag things where suspicions are raised. As an experienced writer, Shelley would know many of such flags were tentative, a legitimate response being to reject them after a cursory mental check - which she probably did in this instance, if it ever happened. For sure, iffy crit is a pain and any crit can be demoralising when you get a downpour (I&amp;#39;d be one of many reviewers doing this). But the patience of Job and thick skin are job requirements.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any road... I do hope I did get some clear and accurate terminology nailed down for POC/MVC. Neutral language in the sense of not carrying misleading baggage. What I&amp;#39;m after is more like &amp;quot;demonstration of utility&amp;quot;. &lt;strong&gt;Clunky, eh&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Semem Demonstration of Utility&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I delighted myself with the hubris I got into my working description of #:semem :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/danja/semem&quot;&gt;Semem&lt;/a&gt; is an LLM-compatible context-aware, open-ended graph knowledgebase system combining the advantages of vector embeddings and Linked Data technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But what am I aiming for by 2025-01-14? I actually have an immediate use case with low-end requirements :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A system I can point to my local FS containing scattered markdown notes etc etc so I can use the stuff efficiently.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I reckon a baseline #:Semem needs to :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;provide simple similarity search&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;cluster related topics at different scales&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;create quasi-formalised annotation (metadata)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;make a disorganised, heterogenous corpus addressable as a coherent entity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;exploit LLMs (and maybe trad reasoning) to facilitate new knowledge discovery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok, I have some actionables. Mari&amp;#39;s picking me up in 15 mins to go for a coffee and I&amp;#39;m not yet out of bed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-30_todos</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-30_todos.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-30_todos.html</id>
        <updated>2024-12-31T10:52:28.627Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Todos&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;No todos los trabajos&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oddments for &lt;strong&gt;soon&lt;/strong&gt; I might easily forget.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:foaf from wget &lt;a href=&quot;https://prod-dcd-datasets-cache-zipfiles.s3.eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/zp23s23xpb-1.zip&quot;&gt;https://prod-dcd-datasets-cache-zipfiles.s3.eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/zp23s23xpb-1.zip&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo check pivot terms - write for #:PoggiPivot &amp;amp; #:ProofPivot. Use &amp;#39;inflection point&amp;#39; in docs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo form-a-matic - make my index.rdf&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo #:squirt to #:tbox&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo #:semem to #:tbox&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo block diagrams - Claude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo pull descriptions from memoripy &amp;amp; trustgraph&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo GitHub ci/CD&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo docker dev env&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo #:postcraft CSS initial size&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo #:postcraft fix links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo #:postcraft figure out #:semtags flow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#:todo #:transmissions generate type definitions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-30_semem-sparq</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-30_semem-sparq.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-30_semem-sparq.html</id>
        <updated>2024-12-31T10:52:28.627Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Semem SPARQ&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/danja/semem&quot;&gt;Semem&lt;/a&gt; doesn&amp;#39;t quite SPARQL yet&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was able to sort out the Faiss API issues from earlier so dove right ahead in implementing storage for #:semem that uses a remote SPARQL endpoint. Well, not quite -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-sh&quot;&gt;Executed 45 of 45 specs (4 ERRORS) (33 FAILED) in 1 sec.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/danja/semem/blob/main/src/SPARQLExample.js&quot;&gt;SPARQLExample.js&lt;/a&gt; also fails miserably, when it tries to &lt;code&gt;UPDATE&lt;/code&gt;. This might well be a problem with the target SPARQL store (Fuseki in the #:tbox Docker), I only set that up yesterday (?), haven&amp;#39;t tested it properly yet. I suspect &lt;strong&gt;auth&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As usual Claude did most of the donkey work for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/danja/semem/blob/main/src/stores/SPARQLStore.js&quot;&gt;SPARQLStore.js&lt;/a&gt; (and there&amp;#39;s a &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/danja/semem/blob/main/src/stores/CachedSPARQLStore.js&quot;&gt;CachedSPARQLStore.js&lt;/a&gt;) just use simple templating to create the SPARQL. But that&amp;#39;s all it needs right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-javascript&quot;&gt;_generateInsertStatements(memories, type) {
    return memories.map((interaction, index) =&amp;gt; `
        _:interaction${type}${index} a mcp:Interaction ;
            mcp:id &amp;quot;${interaction.id}&amp;quot; ;
            mcp:prompt &amp;quot;${this._escapeSparqlString(interaction.prompt)}&amp;quot; ;
            mcp:output &amp;quot;${this._escapeSparqlString(interaction.output)}&amp;quot; ;
            mcp:embedding &amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;${JSON.stringify(interaction.embedding)}&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot; ;
            mcp:timestamp &amp;quot;${interaction.timestamp}&amp;quot;^^xsd:integer ;
            mcp:accessCount &amp;quot;${interaction.accessCount}&amp;quot;^^xsd:integer ;
            mcp:concepts &amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;${JSON.stringify(interaction.concepts)}&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot; ;
            mcp:decayFactor &amp;quot;${interaction.decayFactor}&amp;quot;^^xsd:decimal ;
            mcp:memoryType &amp;quot;${type}&amp;quot; .
    `).join(&amp;#39;&#92;n&amp;#39;);
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, I finally found a use for the &lt;a href=&quot;https://purl.org/stuff/mcp&quot;&gt;Model Context Protocol Ontology&lt;/a&gt; Claude &amp;amp; I put together almost a month ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-30_semem-lives</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-30_semem-lives.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-30_semem-lives.html</id>
        <updated>2024-12-31T10:52:28.627Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Semem Lives!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/danja/semem&quot;&gt;Semem&lt;/a&gt; &lt;del&gt;is&lt;/del&gt; will be an LLM-compatible context-aware, open-ended graph knowledgebase system combining the advantages of vector embeddings and Linked Data technologies.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-29_semem-ollama.html&quot;&gt;Notes from yesterday&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-30_perplexed.html&quot;&gt;this morning&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wow!&lt;/strong&gt;, that went remarkably well. I&amp;#39;m pretty familiar with the semweb bits, the embedding/chat interfacing side very inexperienced. So, hard part (for me) first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Claude did most of the heavy lifting, a long session about a month ago, a bunch this morning. I only actually &lt;strong&gt;ran it for the first time about an hour ago&lt;/strong&gt;. Predictably Claude had left me with a load of manual &lt;em&gt;make-sane&lt;/em&gt; refactoring to do. One stumble remaining is down to Faiss libs. The npm package &lt;code&gt;faiss&lt;/code&gt; is an empty repo, Claude had hallucinated its API. What I needed was &lt;code&gt;faiss-node&lt;/code&gt;. So that&amp;#39;s where it stalls right now. I&amp;#39;ve got the tooling in place to quicky sort this out. But I&amp;#39;d used up my Claude Pro (!) token allowance by 11am, it&amp;#39;s not due to reset for 20 mins and I have at least one tree to cut down before it gets dark...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still embryonic, but so pleasing, in &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/danja/semem/blob/main/src/OllamaExample.js&quot;&gt;OllamaExample.js&lt;/a&gt; there is :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-javascript&quot;&gt;chat: {
    provider: &amp;#39;ollama&amp;#39;,
    model: &amp;#39;qwen2:1.5b&amp;#39;
},
embedding: {
    provider: &amp;#39;ollama&amp;#39;,
    model: &amp;#39;nomic-embed-text&amp;#39;
}
...
    const prompt = &amp;quot;What&amp;#39;s the current state of AI technology?&amp;quot;;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;...and so...&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-sh&quot;&gt;node src/OllamaExample.js

[INFO] Generating embedding...
[INFO] No existing interaction history found in JSON. Starting fresh.
[INFO] Memory initialized with 0 short-term and 0 long-term memories
[INFO] Extracting concepts...
[INFO] Extracted concepts: [ &amp;#39;AI technology&amp;#39; ]
[INFO] No interactions available
Response: AI (artificial intelligence) technology has come a long way since its inception in the 1950s. It is now a rapidly growing field, and there are numerous advancements being made across various industries.

1. Machine Learning: This involves programming computers to learn from data without being explicitly programmed. It&amp;#39;s used for tasks like recognizing images, identifying voice commands, or predicting customer behavior.

2. Natural Language Processing (NLP): AI systems can understand human language in ways that make them easier to interact with and more efficient. They are used for tasks like chatbots, virtual assistants, and text-based search engines.

3. Robotics: As technology develops further, robots have become better at performing complex tasks autonomously. Some advanced robots now perform jobs such as manufacturing goods or even medical procedures.

4. Computer Vision (CV): This uses AI to help computers understand visual information in images or videos. It&amp;#39;s used for applications like self-driving cars, security cameras, and facial recognition.

5. Deep Learning: This branch of artificial intelligence involves creating algorithms that can learn from data without being explicitly programmed. It&amp;#39;s widely used in image classification tasks, natural language processing, and reinforcement learning.

6. Neural Networks: These are a type of machine learning algorithm inspired by the human brain. They&amp;#39;re used for tasks such as recognizing handwriting, speech recognition, and playing games like chess or Go.

In summary, AI technology is advancing rapidly across various fields, offering more efficient solutions to complex problems. However, there&amp;#39;s still room for improvement in areas like ethical considerations and ensuring that AI systems can be trusted by humans.
[INFO] Generating embedding...
[INFO] Extracting concepts...
[INFO] Extracted concepts: [
  &amp;#39;Machine Learning&amp;#39;,
  &amp;#39;Natural Language Processing (NLP)&amp;#39;,
  &amp;#39;Robotics&amp;#39;,
  &amp;#39;Computer Vision (CV)&amp;#39;,
  &amp;#39;Deep Learning&amp;#39;,
  &amp;#39;Neural Networks&amp;#39;
]
[INFO] Adding interaction: &amp;#39;What&amp;#39;s the current state of AI technology?&amp;#39;
TypeError: Invalid the first argument type, must be an Array.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tree time.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Entry 2024-12-30_perplexed</title>
        <link href="https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-30_perplexed.html"/>
        <id>https://danny.ayers.name/entries/2024-12-30_perplexed.html</id>
        <updated>2024-12-31T10:52:28.627Z</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;!-- POST CONTENT TEMPLATE --&gt;

&lt;article class=&quot;post-content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Perplexed&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Before getting out of bed, I signed up for a free month of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.perplexity.ai/&quot;&gt;Perplexity&lt;/a&gt; and perplexed Claude&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Paths&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; A note-to-self before I forget.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; #:todo check how the &lt;a href=&quot;https://eyereasoner.github.io/eye/&quot;&gt;EYE&lt;/a&gt; reasoner uses &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Leonhard_Euler&quot;&gt;Euler&lt;/a&gt; paths for #:semem&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I had a few overlapping requirements for a classical reasoner. Long story short, I found &lt;a href=&quot;https://eyereasoner.github.io/eye/&quot;&gt;EYE&lt;/a&gt; ticked many boxes. Notably it&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Semantic_Web&quot;&gt;semantic Web&lt;/a&gt;-friendly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a lot of unknowns (in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/There_are_unknown_unknowns&quot;&gt;Donald Rumsfeld senses&lt;/a&gt;) around #:semem. I might have a short summary of what I&amp;#39;m after :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Semem is an LLM-compatible context-aware, open-ended graph knowledgebase combining the advantages of vector embeddings and Linked Data technologies.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now I&amp;#39;m still on the nuts &amp;amp; bolts, I&amp;#39;ve got fairly straightforward next steps to implement before the fun starts. The fun has many dimensions. From the above,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LLM-compatible&lt;/strong&gt; - this starts with boilerplate connectors to Ollama, the OpenAI API, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anthropic.com/news/model-context-protocol&quot;&gt;Model Context Protocol&lt;/a&gt; etc. But an aspect of the &lt;em&gt;open-ended&lt;/em&gt; I have in mind more broadly is exploring connectivity from a different perspective, that of inter-agent comms. This will go under the umbrella of #:LinguaFranche.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;open-ended graph&lt;/strong&gt; - this is the Web. Low-hanging fruit is hooking into existing SPARQL endpoints, eg. WikiData&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;context-aware&lt;/strong&gt; - I&amp;#39;m working on the vocabulary around this to express it more clearly, but the general idea is that you want more relevant knowledge getting more attention&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vector embeddings offer similarity measures, but the RDF (Web) model offers a whole different dimension.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grrr! I went to LinkedIn to find a ref. related to this, instant distractions :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/2411.03252&quot;&gt;Spontaneous Emergence of Agent Individuality through Social Interactions in LLM-Based Communities&lt;/a&gt; [sent to printer for later]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chimezie.medium.com/declarative-prompts-llm-agents-and-their-programs-oh-my-aab1d0da6fef&quot;&gt;Declarative Prompts, LLM Agents, and their Programs. Oh my…&lt;/a&gt; [from Chimezie, left open in tab for sooner]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A ref I can remember offhand is Bergi&amp;#39;s material :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bergnet.org/2024/05/unified-landscape/&quot;&gt;Unveiling the Unified Landscape: Bridging Knowledge Graphs and Machine Learning&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bergnet.org/2024/09/llm-kg-wombat/&quot;&gt;Language Models Meet Knowledge Graphs - A Powerful Duo (plus a Wombat)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;linked from there&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://towardsdatascience.com/how-to-implement-graph-rag-using-knowledge-graphs-and-vector-databases-60bb69a22759&quot;&gt;How to Implement Graph RAG Using Knowledge Graphs and Vector Databases&lt;/a&gt; - Steve Hedden&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#:todo put some FOAF where &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bergnet.org/people/bergi/card&quot;&gt;Bergi&amp;#39;s card&lt;/a&gt; links to it : &lt;a href=&quot;http://danny.ayers.name/index.rdf#me&quot;&gt;http://danny.ayers.name/index.rdf#me&lt;/a&gt;
#:todo W6 link on &lt;a href=&quot;https://hyperdata.it/xmlns/&quot;&gt;https://hyperdata.it/xmlns/&lt;/a&gt; is broken - make broken link finder #:transmission?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enough gab, I&amp;#39;d better get on with this thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/article&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;post-title h-cinzel&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
</feed>